A Guide to the Papers of William Belser Spong, 1957-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- SERIES III: PAPERS RE THE U.S. SENATE
  - SUBSERIES A: LEGISLATIVE FILES
    - Foreign Relations Subcommittee Preferences 1971 (Box 27)
    - Fortas, Abe - Nomination to the Supreme Court 1968-1970 (Box 27)
    - Four Mile Run Flood Control Project 1965-1971, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Frank, John P.: Lecture and Correspondence re "Ruminations on Reason and Law: A Spong Song" 1971 (Box 27)
    - Haynsworth, Clement - Nomination to the Supreme Court, including a Richard Nixon letter 1969 November 21 1969-1970, 4 folders (Box 28)
    - Hopkins, William B. - Dinner 1968 August 4 (Box 28)
    - Hunger in Virginia 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Impact Aid Reform Act of 1970 1968-1970 (Box 29)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration Grants - Requirement for the "Buy-In" Matching Contributions by the State 1971-1972 (Box 29)
    - Legislative-Judicial: Committee for Diversity Jurisdiction 1971 (Box 29)
    - Majority Whip Votes 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Mental Health Chronology 1967-1969 (Box 30)
    - Middle East Chronology 1967-1971, n.d., 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Minimum Wage 1971-1972 (Box 30)
    - Minority Hiring and Employment Practices in the Senate Office 1967 & 1972 (Box 30)
    - Motivation Study, Willcox and Zaleznik for the U.S. Department of Labor 1968 (Box 30)
    - National Defense Education Act 1966-1968 (Box 30)
    - National School Desegregation Act (S. 4167) 1970 (Box 30)
    - National School Desegregation Act (S. 4167) 1970 (Box 31)
    - National School Lunch Programs 1967-1969 (Box 31)
    - No Fault Insurance Legislation 1971-1972, n.d., 2 folders (Box 31)
    - No Fault Insurance Notebook n.d. (Box 31)
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organization 1967-1969 (Box 31)
    - Open Housing Legislation 1968 (Box 31)
    - Personal Financial Disclosure Statements 1968-1972 (Box 31)
    - Powell, Lewis F., Jr. - Nomination to the Supreme Court 1969, 1971, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - "Lewis F. Powell, Jr. Selected Speeches and Articles" 1971 October 27 (Box 32)
    - Prayer in Public Schools - Constitutional Amendment 1966 (Box 32)
    - Ratings of Senatorial Voting Records by Special Interest Groups 1966-1972 (Box 32)
    - Roll Call Vote Camparison of Spong with Other Senators 1967-1972 (Box 33)
    - Salem Church Dam Project Salem Church Dam Project, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Smith, Ian: Denial of Visa to the United States 1967-1968 (Box 33)
    - Sports Anti-Trust 1971 (Box 33)
    - State Highway Commission: Richard S. Holland and Mills Godwin 1966-1967 (Box 33)
    - Steering Committee 1970-1972 (Box 33)
    - Strategic Arms Limitation Agreements 1972 (Box 33)
    - Toxic Substances 1970-1972, n.d., 2 folders (Box 34)
    - University of Virginia Student Unrest 1970 (Box 34)
    - Vietnam Background 1964-1972, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Voting Rights 1965-1971, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Wage Board Legislation 1970-1972, n.d. (Box 35)
    - War Powers Legislation 1968-1971, n.d., 2 folders (Box 35)
    - York River Oil Pollution 1966-1970 (Box 35)
    - Young Democratic Clubs Convention, Norfolk, Virginia 1967 March-May (Box 35)
  - SUBSERIES B: NEWSCLIPPINGS RE LEGISLATION AND RELATED MATTERS
    - Newsclippings: Defense and Foreign Affairs ca. 1967-1972 (Box 36)
    - Newsclippings: Economy and Finance ca. 1967-1972 (Box 36)
    - Newsclippings: Education - Busing ca. 1967-1972 (Box 36)
    - Newsclippings: Education - Desegregation ca. 1967-1972 (Box 36)
    - Newsclippings: Education - Miscellaneous ca. 1967-1972 (Box 36)
    - Newsclippings: Environment & Consumer Affairs ca. 1967-1972 (Box 36)
    - ca. 1967-1972 ca. 1967-1972 (Box 36)
    - Newsclippings: Health & Welfare ca. 1967-1972 (Box 36)
    - Newsclippings: Judiciary - Carswell Nomination ca. 1967-1972 (Box 37)
    - Newsclippings: Judiciary - Miscellaneous ca. 1967-1972 (Box 37)
    - Newsclippings: Special Coverage ca. 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 37)
    - Newsclippings: Transportation ca. 1967-1972 (Box 37)
- SERIES IV: NON-SENATORIAL ACTIVITIES OF WILLIAM B. SPONG
  - SUBSERIES A: COMMISSION ON THE ORGANIZATION OF THE GOVERNMENT
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy 1973-1975 May, 5 folders (Box 38)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy 1975 July-1976 January, n.d. (Box 39)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Access of the Press to Information (Box 39)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Briefing 1974 (Box 39)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Business Session 1973-1974 (Box 39)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Employee Matters 1973-1975 (Box 39)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Integrative Phase 1974 (Box 39)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Joint Committee on National Security 1974 September-1975 February, 3 folders (Box 39)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Joint Committee on National Security 1975 February (Box 40)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Miscellaneous Correspondence 1973-1975 (Box 40)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Panels 1974 April-May, 3 folders (Box 40)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Public Hearings 1974 (Box 40)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Reply to Senator Proxmire's Letter re Federal Advisory Councils 1973-1974 (Box 40)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Report (Printed 1975 June (Box 41)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Supporting Documents 1973-1974 (Box 41)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Virginia Law Review Article by Louis Henkin 1974-1975 (Box 41)
    - Commission ... For the Conduct of Foreign Policy: Working Papers Sent to Members of the Congressional Committee 1974-1975, (2 folders (Box 41)
  - SUBSERIES B: GOVERNOR'S COMMISSION ON VIRGINIA'S FUTURE
    - 1. MEETINGS (Box 41)
      - Richmond 1982 November 11 (Box 42)
      - Charlottesville 1982 December 9 (Box 42)
      - Blacksburg 1983 January 6 (Box 42)
      - Richmond 1983 January 11 (Box 42)
      - Richmond 1983 February 3 (Box 42)
      - Williamsburg 1983 March 3 (Box 42)
      - Wintergreen 1983 April 6-7 (Box 42)
      - Charlottesville 1983 May 5 (Box 43)
      - Richmond 1983 June 2 (Box 43)
      - Fredericksburg 1983 July 7 (Box 43)
      - Charlottesville 1983 August 4 (Box 43)
      - Richmond 1983 September 8, 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Richmond 1983 October 6 (Box 44)
      - Richmond 1983 November 3 (Box 44)
      - Richmond 1983 December 1 (Box 44)
      - Richmond 1984 January 5 (Box 44)
      - Richmond 1984 February 2 (Box 44)
      - Richmond 1984 March 1, 1 of 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Richmond 1984 March 1, 2 of 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Richmond 1984 April 12 (Box 45)
      - Smith Mountain Lake 1984 May 3 (Box 45)
      - Hampden-Sydney 1984 June 7 (Box 45)
      - University of Virginia 1984 July 9 & 10 (Box 45)
      - Gunston Hall 1984 August 2 (Box 45)
      - Wakefield 1984 September 6 (Box 45)
      - Gloucester 1984 October 2 (Box 45)
      - Charlottesville 1984 October 18 (Box 45)
    - 2. RELATED MATERIAL
      - Final Report (Galleys) 1984 November 8 (Box 46)
      - Final Report (Printed) 1984 December (Box 46)
      - Material re Final Report 1982 & 1984 (Box 46)
      - Membership of the Commission 1982 (Box 46)
      - Memorandum for Governor Robb from Tim Sullivan 1982 June 4 (Box 46)
      - Miscellaneous and Newsclippings 1983-1985 (Box 46)
      - Notebook of Preliminary Information 1980-1982 (Box 46)
      - Summary of Meetings & Index of Reports 1982-1984 (Box 47)
      - Summary of Public Comment Inquiries and Responses 1983-1984 (Box 47)
      - Working Draft of Report 1984 (Box 47)
  - SUBSERIES C: MISCELLANEOUS TOPICAL
    - The American Assembly, Stanford Law School 1975 (Box 47)
    - American Bar Association: Coalition for Adequate Judicial Compensation 1975 (Box 47)
    - Banking Laws: Changes 1963 (Box 47)
    - Civil War Centennial Commission 1960-1964 (Box 47)
    - Commission on the Future of the South 1986 (Box 47)
    - Commonwealth Election Fund 1977-1980 (Box 48)
    - Conference of State Court Administrators: Federalism as a Developing Concept 1987-1988 (Box 48)
    - Educational Television 1961-1962 (Box 48)
    - Form Letter re the Campaign Deficit of Andrew Miller 1977 (Box 48)
    - Forum Club 1985 (Box 48)
    - 4th Congressional Seat Race: Draft Spong Movement 1973-1974 (Box 48)
    - General Assembly Election of 1963 1963 (Box 48)
    - General Assembly Election of 1965 1965 (Box 48)
    - General Assembly: Legislative Concerns 1961-1962 (Box 48)
    - Governor's Commission on Excellence in Education: Report 1986 (Box 48)
    - Hampden-Sydney College: Dr. L. Neel Beard 1974 (Box 49)
    - Hampden-Sydney College: Symposium on Law 1973, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Highway Safety 1964 (Box 49)
    - The Institute For Congress 1975 March-1978 October, 3 folders (Box 49)
    - Institute of Government, Winchester, Virginia: Court Days 1985-1986 (Box 50)
    - National Center for State Courts Reception 1977-1978 (Box 50)
    - National War College Course: "The Congress and U.S. National Security Policy Formulation" 1976-1977 (Box 50)
    - Newsclippings - General 1973-1986 (Box 50)
    - North Carolina Bar Association Annual Meeting 1976 (Box 50)
    - Old Dominion University Media Interviews 1973 (Box 50)
    - Portsmouth General Hospital 1972-1976 (Box 50)
    - Portsmouth Historic Foundation ca. 1957-1976 (Box 50)
    - Portsmouth Judgeship 1962-1963 (Box 50)
    - Portsmouth Notable Occasion Dinner 1987 October 16 (Box 50)
    - Southern Conference of Bar Presidents 1977 July (Box 50)
    - Spong Staff Reunion 1987-1988 (Box 50)
    - Texas Law Review Article re Spong 1971 (Box 50)
    - Tidewater Funeral Directors Association 1974-1975 (Box 50)
    - Uninsured Motorist Act 1962 (Box 50)
    - United States Circuit Judge Nominating Commission 1977-1978, n.d., 3 folders (Box 51)
    - University of Richmond Law School 1974-1976 (Box 51)
    - University of Virginia John A. Ewald, Jr., Distinguished Visiting Professor of Law 1986-1987 (Box 52)
    - University of Virginia Seminars 1970-1973 (Box 52)
    - Virginia Association of Economists 1985 (Box 52)
    - Virginia Citizens Planning Association 1983 (Box 52)
    - Virginia Commission on Campaign Financing 1973-1974 (Box 52)
    - Virginia Society for the Blind 1976 (Box 52)
    - Washington & Lee Honorary Degree 1986 (Box 52)
    - Woodrow Wilson Birthplace Foundation 1974 (Box 52)
  - SUBSERIES D: VIRGINIA BAR ASSOCIATION
    - Advertising of Lawyer Services 1975-1976 (Box 53)
    - Annual Winter Meeting 1976-1977 (Box 53)
    - Bicentennial Committee on the Constitution 1976, 1985-1988 (Box 53)
    - Button v Day 1962-1963 (Box 53)
    - Committee on Lawyer Professionalism 1984-1985, n.d., 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Committee on Lawyer Professionalism 1986 (Box 54)
    - Constitution and By-Laws Revision 1974-1977 (Box 54)
    - Executive Committee 1977-1978 (Box 54)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, October 29, 30, 1976 1976 (Box 54)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, January 13, 1977 1975-1977 (Box 54)
    - Legislation 1962 (Box 55)
    - Mandatory Continuing Legal Education 1975-1977 (Box 55)
    - Panel on Political Lawyers 1977 (Box 55)
    - Pledge to the National Center for State Courts 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Program for the Williamsburg Meeting 1975-1976 (Box 55)
    - Resolution on Chief Justice John Eggleston 1976 September-October (Box 55)
    - Special Committee on Ethics and UPL Opinions (Formerly Goldfarb Committee) 1976 (Box 55)
    - Summer Meeting Program July 15, 1976 1976 (Box 55)
    - Surety Title Insurance Agency, Inc. 1976 May-September (Box 56)
    - Survey "Public Attitudes Towards Lawyers in Virginia" 1975-1977, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Talks 1975 (Box 56)
    - Virginia Bar Association Journal 1975-1977 (Box 56)
    - Woodberry Forest Meeting 1976 (Box 56)
    - Young Lawyers Film on the Supreme Court 1976 (Box 56)
  - SUBSERIES E: VIRGINIA COMMISSION ON PUBLIC EDUCATION
    - General Files 1959-1962, n.d., 4 folders (Box 57)
    - Henrico County Curriculum Study 1959-1961 (Box 57)
    - Machine Teaching 1959-1961 (Box 57)
    - Physical Education n.d. (Box 57)
    - Printed Material 1958-1962 (Box 58)
    - Reading 1960-1961, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Reports 1960-1961, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Special Education 1960, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Summary of Statements Made as a Result of the Public Hearings 1961 February (Box 58)
    - Teacher Training 1960-1961 (Box 58)
    - Trips 1961 (Box 58)
    - Virginia High School League 1960-1961 (Box 58)
  - SUBSERIES F: WILLIAM AND MARY
    - American Bar Association Hearing in Chicago re the School of Law 1973-1976, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Bicentennial of American Legal Education 1976 (Box 59)
    - Commencement Address 1985 (Box 59)
    - General Assembly 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Law Deanship 1975 (Box 59)
    - Law Faculty By-Laws 1976 (Box 60)
    - Law School Building 1975-1976 (Box 60)
    - Law School Dedication 1980 (Box 60)
    - Letters of Congratulations 1975-1976, 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Portrait of Dean Spong 1985-1986 (Box 60)
    - Presidency 1983-1984 (Box 60)
    - Printed and Miscellaneous Material ca. 1975-1986 (Box 60)
    - Retirement of Dean Spong 1984-1986, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - School of Law Groundbreaking Ceremony 1976 (Box 61)
    - Special Legislation For Faculty Salary Increments 1982-1984 (Box 61)
    - Speech re "Spong the Man" [ca. 1985 ?] (Box 61)
    - Virginia Bar Association Committee 1975-1976 (Box 61)
- SERIES V: SPEECHES AND ARTICLES
  - Blacksburg Bicentennial Committee Speech re Virginia's Ratification of the U.S. Constitution 1987 (Box 61)
  - Clue Magazine Interview with Senator Spong 1985 (Box 61)
  - First Citizen's Award: Introduction for Richard J. Davis 1974 (Box 61)
  - Goucher College Speech 1986 April 15 (Box 61)
  - Hampden-Sydney College Keynote Address 1976 March 6 (Box 61)
  - Institute of the Bill of Rights Law Speech: "The Public's Right to Know" 1987 November 12 (Box 61)
  - Mabel Brown Memorial Lecture "India," Norfolk Society of Arts, Chrysler Museum 1978 October 24 (Box 61)
  - Miscellaneous Interviews with Frank Atkinson, Henry Foresman, Jr. and David Steen 1983-1986 (Box 61)
  - National Defense University Lecture 1977 June 23 (Box 61)
  - Newport News Bar Association Bicentennial Committee: Law Day Address 1976 (Box 61)
  - Old Dominion University Lecture 1973 November (Box 61)
  - Richmond Hampden-Sydney Alumni Meeting Address, Commonwealth Club 1978 November 7 (Box 61)
  - Richmond Rotary Club Speech 1961 March 28 (Box 61)
  - Salzburg Seminar 1979 July (Box 62)
  - Speeches: Miscellaneous 1959-1968, n.d. (Box 62)
  - Statewide Conference on Food and Nutrition: Introduction of Esther Peterson 1979 November 27-28 (Box 62)
  - University of Richmond Law Review Article: "Can Balance Be Restored in the Constitutional War Powers of the President and Congress?" 1971, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - University of Richmond Law Review Book Review of Commentaries on the Constitution of Virginia 1975 (Box 62)
  - University of Virginia Alumni News Article: "Ruminations on Ratification" 1988 May-June (Box 62)
  - University of Virginia Law Day Speech 1976 (Box 62)
  - University of Virginia Law Day Speech 1986-1987 (Box 62)
  - University of Virginia Oral History Interview 1980 (Box 62)
  - University of Virginia School of Law Student Legal Forum Annual Banquet Speech 1988 (Box 63)
  - University of Virginia Summer on the Lawn Speech: re the Virginia Ratification Convention 1987 (Box 63)
  - University of Virginia White Burkett Miller Center of Public Affairs Speech re Constitutional Convention of 1788 1988 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Associated Press Newspapers Association Speech 1984-1985 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Bar Association Journal Article: "John Marshall -- the Early Years" 1988 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Forum Article on the Constitutional Convention 1986 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities and Public Policy: Lecture re the "Public's Right to Know" 1987 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Historical Society Book Review - The First Hundred Years re the University of Virginia Law School 1979 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Law Review Book Review: War Powers of the President and Congress: Who Holds the Arrows and Olive Branch? 1982 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Law Weekly Dicta Article - "Money and Politics" 1973 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Lawyers Weekly: "State's Vote Key to Constitution's Adoption" 1987 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Military Institute Constitutional Symposium Keynote Speech 1976 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Pilot Interview 1973 September 19 (Box 63)
  - Virginia Tidal and Coastal Law Foreword 1988 (Box 63)
  - Washington and Lee University Social Responsibility- "The Perjurious Criminal Client" 1976-1988, n.d., 3 folders (Box 64)
  - William and Mary Law Review Article - "The War Powers Resolution Revisited: Historic Accomplishment or Surrender ?" 1970-1975, n.d., 3 folders (Box 64)
  - William and Mary Speech 1974 February 22 (Box 65)
  - Woodberry Forest School Commencement Address 1978 June (Box 65)
- SERIES VI: PHOTOGRAPHS AND SLIDES
  - Business and Labor 1972, n.d. (Box 65)
  - Campaign 1966, 1972 (Box 65)
  - Democratic Party and Political 1967-1972 (Box 65)
  - Drug Trip 1972 July (Box 65)
  - Foreign Affairs and Trips 1968-1971 (Box 65)
  - Health 1971-1972 (Box 65)
  - Meetings of Clubs, Conventions, Other Organizations and Dedications 1967-1972, n.d. (Box 65)
  - Military 1966-1972, n.d. (Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous ca. 1967-1972 (Box 66)
  - Personalities ca. 1967-1972 (Box 66)
  - Schools, Colleges, and Students ca. 1967-1972 (Box 66)
  - Senate Hearings re Federal Aid Disaster Relief During Hurricane Camille (August 1969) in Roanoke, Virginia with an on site Inspection Tour 1970 January (Box 66)
  - Senator Spong ca. 1966-1972 (Box 66)
  - Virginia Spong and the Spong Family 1968, n.d. (Box 66)
  - Transportation 1968-1972, n.d. (Box 66)
  - Young People with Spong 1967-1972, n.d. (Box 66)
  - Slides - Miscellaneous 1968-1972 (Box 66)
- SERIES VII: MICROFILMS, COMPUTER DATA TAPES & REEL TO REEL TAPE RECORDINGS, 16 mm microfilms (Box 67-70)
  The microfilms included in this accession have been divided into three groups:
  Constituent Correspondence ("Yellow Carbons"): Reels 1 - 42
  [Constituents] Master Address List: Reels 43 - 54
  Miscellaneous: Reels 55-59
  - CONSTITUENT CORRESPONDENCE ("Yellow Carbons") (Reel 1-42)
    This series consists of copies of retained copies of letters sent to constituents, alphabetically arranged by last name. The correspondence for 1967-1970 and 1971 were filmed separately; the first group (reels 1-12) is incomplete, but the second group (reels 13-42) appears complete. The year given in parentheses denotes the primary year of the correspondence included, but the researcher should bear in mind that correspondence for other years does appear on the films, including the period 1967-70 in the 1971 series.
    The researcher should note also that the microfilms were prepared in duplicate (variations in the inclusive names listed may be presumed to be clerical errors.) As the material filmed were carbon copies on yellow paper, the image quality is less than optimum. Since the image quality varies from one microfilm copy to the other, both copies have been retained in the collection, and researchers should check both copies in instances where particular letters are difficult to read.
    - ABBOTT - ANSPAUGH 1967-70 (1967) (Reel 1)
    - ABBOTT - ANABELES 1967-70 (1967) (Reel 2)
    - APTER - BARRETT 1967-70 (1967) (Reel 3)
    - APTER - BARRETT 1967-70 (1967) (Reel 4)
    - BARRICK - BOARDMAN 1967-70 (1969) (Reel 5)
    - BARRY - BOARDMAN 1967-70 (1969) (Reel 6)
    - 1967-70
    - BOARD - BROGAN 1967-70 (1967) (Reel 7)
    - BOARD - BROGAN 1967-70 (1967) (Reel 8)
    - BROOKS - CALHOUN 1967-70 (1967) (Reel 9)
    - BROOKS - CALHOUN 1967-70 (1969) (Reel 10)
    - CALLAHAN - CAPPELEAR 1967-70 (1968) (Reel 11)
    - CALLAHAN - CHAPPELEAR 1967-70 (1968) (Reel 12)
    - AARONSON - BELL 1971 (Reel 13)
    - AARONSON - BELLER 1971 (Reel 14)
    - BELF - BUTTS 1971 (Reel 15)
    - BELFORD - BUTTS 1971 (Reel 16)
    - BUTT - COX 1971 (Reel 17)
    - BUTT - COX 1971 (Reel 18)
    - COX - ELLIS 1971 (Reel 19)
    - COX - ELLIS 1971 (Reel 20)
    - ELLIOTT - GLASS 1971 (Reel 21)
    - ELLIOTT - GLASS 1971 (Reel 22)
    - GLEASON - HEBERT 1971 (Reel 23)
    - GLEASON - HENRY 1971 (Reel 24)
    - HEPBURN - JUSTICE 1971 (Reel 25)
    - HEPBURN - JUSTICE 1971 (Reel 26)
    - KAFKA - LUDWIG 1971 (Reel 27)
    - KAFKA - LUDWIG 1971 (Reel 28)
    - LUCK - MILLER 1971 (Reel 29)
    - LUCK - MILLER 1971 (Reel 30)
    - MILLS - PENCE 1971 (Reel 31)
    - MILLS - PENCE 1971 (Reel 32)
    - PENLEY - ROY 1971 (Reel 33)
    - PENLEY - ROY 1971 (Reel 34)
    - ROWE - SPATHOS 1971 (Reel 35)
    - ROWE - SPATHOS 1971 (Reel 36)
    - SPARKS - VAN KOPPENHAGE 1971 (Reel 37)
    - SPARKS - VAN KOPPENHAGE 1971 (Reel 38)
    - VAN HOOK - WRIGHT 1971 (Reel 39)
    - VAN HOOK - WRIGHT 1971 (Reel 40)
    - WRIGHT - ZUMWALT 1971 (Reel 41)
    - WRIGHT - ZUMWALT 1971 (Reel 42)
  - [CONSTITUENTS] MASTER ADDRESS LIST (Reel 43-54)
    The microfilms in this group were produced on March 2, 1972, and consist of a complete list in alphabetical order by name of all [constituent correspondence, 1967-1972]. Besides standard directory information, coded information, including the addressee's profession, is listed.
    - AARDEMAN, Herman - BOURDEAUX, John 1967-72 (Reel 43)
    - BOURDEAUX, John - COCHRANE, Wilma 1967-72 (Reel 44)
    - COCRONE, Charles - DUCKETT, George 1967-72 (Reel 45)
    - DUCKETT, Gladys - GLASS, Blair 1967-72 (Reel 46)
    - GLASS, Bobby - HOLLAND, Addie 1967-72 (Reel 47)
    - HOLLAND, Alan - KINTNER, Edwin 1967-72 (Reel 48)
    - KINTNER, Eric - McNEALY, Dorothy 1967-72 (Reel 49)
    - McNEALY, M.R. - PANNELL, C.A. 1967-72 (Reel 50)
    - PANNELL, C.E. - ROBERTS, Courtland 1967-72 (Reel 51)
    - ROBERTS, David - SOLES, J. 1967-72 (Reel 52)
    - SOLES, Lucy - WADE, C.A. 1967-72 (Reel 53)
    - WADE, Callie - Z 1967-72 (Reel 54)
  - MISCELLANEOUS (Reel 55-59)
    - "Compass Voter List" for an unidentified city. The first part lists registered voters by street address, the second part lists them alphabetically by name. 1972 JUN 7 (Reel 55)
    - Hand-written addresses, presumably for a special occasion, arranged alphabetically by name. n.d. (Reel 56)
    - Computer-printed address labels, arranged alphabetically by name within zip code, in two series. n.d. (Reel 57)
    - Petitions signed by registered voters to qualify Sen. Spong for the primary election to be held on June 7, 1972. 1972 (Reel 58)
    - Disability claims submitted by victims of Black Lung disease, with related correspondence. 1970-71 (Reel 59)
  - Computer Data Types (Box 70)
    - "Current" collection of letters ("mini module") n.d. (Reel 1)
    - "#880 vol. 1": master file of [form] letters [1964] (Reel 2)
    - "#880 vol. 2": master file of [form] letters [1965] (Reel 3)
    - "#880 vol. 3": master file of [form] letters 1966 (Reel 4)
    - "#880 vol. 4": master file of [form] letters 1967 (Reel 5)
  - AUDIO TAPE RECORDINGS
    - Primary Election Campaign: "Tape #1" 1966 (Reel T-888)
    - Primary Election Campaign: "Tape #2" 1966 (Reel T-889)
    - Primary Election Campaign: "Closing Speech" [1966] (Reel T-890)
    - Primary Election: "Major speech in Norfolk" n.y. JUN (Reel T-891)
    - "Norfolk Primary: Robertson Major Speech" n.d. (Reel T-892)
    - "Norfolk Primary: Robertson Press Conference" n.d. (Reel T-893)
    - "Primary Roundup News: Tape #1" n.d. (Reel T-894)